Eric W. Lawson Arbitration Files 6366
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Miscellaneous, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Abbot, Tills, and Knapp and Client, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 3)
    November 12, 1987. Bar Association of Erie County case number: 87-540. Opinion and Award regarding attorney's fees.
  - Item 4: Insurance Client and Commercial Union Insurance Company, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 3)
    November 30, 1988. HSA case number: 88-00157. Attorney's Affidavit regarding claims settlement.
- Miscellaneous, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Port Authority of New York and New Jersey and Union of Automotive Technicians (UOAT), 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 4)
    June 11, 1990. Port Authority Employment Relations Panel. Fact Finder's Report and Recommendations regarding collective bargaining impass.
  - Item 2: Buffalo General Hospital and Buffalo and Western New York Hospital and Nursing Home Council, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 4)
    November 15, 1990. Opinion and Award regarding termination.
- Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Better Business Bureau of Western New York and ACE Paving Company, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 5)
    October 14, 1992. Opinion and Award regarding eligibility of volunteer arbitrator.
  - Item 2: Buffalo School Engineers Association and International Union of Operating Engineers, Locals 71, 71A, 71B, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 5)
    April 16, 1993. Opinion and Award regarding suspension.
- Miscellaneous, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Gibralter Steel Corporation and UAW, Local 55, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 6)
    April 1, 1996. New York State Employment Relations Board (SERB). Opinion and Award regarding overtime.
  - Item 2: County of Monroe and Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Local 828, Monroe County Employee Unit, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 6)
    October 26, 1996. Opinion and Award regarding termination.
- Miscellaneous, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: County of Erie and the Erie County Sheriff's Police Benevolent Association (BPA), 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 7)
    September 11, 2000. Opinion and Decision regarding suspension.
  - Item 2: County of Steuben and Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Local 1000, AFSCME for Stueben County Local 851, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 7)
    December 12, 2000. Opinion and Award regarding personal leave.
- Miscellaneous, 2001-2005 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 200-C and the Village of Gowanda, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 8)
    February 20, 2001. Opinion and Decision regarding discharge.
  - Item 2: County of Erie and Teamsters Local 264, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 8)
    February 27, 2002. Case number: 01-0006. Opinion and Award regarding negotiated pay.
  - Item 3: Teamsters Local 118 and Webman's Food Markets, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 8)
    October 30, 2003. Opinion and Award regarding termination.
  - Item 4: County of Chautauqua and Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Local 1000, AFSCME, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 8)
    August 27, 2005. Opinion and Decision regarding termination.
- Miscellaneous, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: US Customs and Border Protection Service and the National Treasury Employees Union, Local 138, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 9)
    March 22, 2006. Opinion and Award regarding suspension.
  - Item 2: US Customs and Border Protection Service and the National Treasury Employees Union, Local 138, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 9)
    March 27, 2006. Opinion and Decision regarding discharge.
  - Item 3: Elmira Water Board and Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Local 6354, Chemung County Local 808, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 9)
    May 21, 2006. Opinion and Award regarding reallocation.
- Miscellaneous, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: County of Saratoga, Saratoga County Sheriff, and Saratoga County Deputy Sheriff's Benevolent Association, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 10)
    January 6, 2007. Opinion and Decision regarding shift exchange and overtime distribution.
  - Item 2: New York State Thruway Authority and Teamsters Local 72, New York State Thruway Employees, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 10)
    September 22, 2008. Opinion and Decision regarding disciplinary hearing.
  - Item 3: Salada Foods/Redco Foods and Bakery, Confectionary, Tobacco Workers' and Grain Millers' Union, Local 50, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 10)
    January 31, 2009. New York State Employment Relations Board (SERB) case number: AP 08-08. Opinion and Decision regarding refusal to reinstate strikers.
  - Item 4: Simmons Machine Tool Corporation and International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers, Local 81981, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 10)
    April 9, 2011. Opinion and Decision regarding termination.
- Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 2014; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Veterans Administration, Mountain Home Tennessee and American Federation of Government Employees, 2014; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 11)
    June 6, 2014. Opinion and Decision regarding seniority.
- Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 2016; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: United States Forest Service and National Federation of Federal Employees, Local 466, 2016; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 12)
    September 1, 2016. Opinion and Decision regarding five day suspension.
  - Item 2: United States Forest Service and National Federation of Federal Employees, Local 466, 2016; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 12)
    November 23, 2016. Petition for Attorney's Fees.
- New York State Department of Education, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Wyantskill Union Free School District and Teacher, 2013; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 13)
    September 17, 2013. Motion to Strike Decision.
  - Item 2: Wyantskill Union Free School District and Teacher, 2014; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 13)
    February 20, 2014. Opinion and Decision regarding misconduct and insubordination.
- State of New York Disciplinary Panel Administration, 2014; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: SUNY Upstate Medical University, 2014; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 14)
    September 14, 2014. Motion to Dismiss regarding discharge.
- New York State Public Employment Relations Board, 2010-2012 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: City of Syracuse New York and Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 15)
    July 20, 2010. Opinion and Decision regarding compensatory time, detective tenure, and overtime calculation rate. 15 pages.
  - Item 2: City of Syracuse New York and Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 15)
    July 20, 2010. Opinion and Decision regarding compensatory time, detective tenure, and overtime calculation rate. 29 pages, incomplete.
  - Item 3: City of Syracuse New York and Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 2012; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 15)
    October 26, 2012. Opinion and Award regarding compensatory time, detective tenure, and overtime calculation rate.
- New York State Public Employment Relations Board, 2014; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: the County of Onondaga and Deputy Sheriffs Benevolent Association of Onondaga County, 2014; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 16)
    March 8, 2014. Opinion and Decision regarding discharge.